>> Kyle Simpson: 从观察角度来定义闭包，而不是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: To define closure from
an observational perspective, rather than
从一个角度来看，这个学术的问题。
from a whether it exists or not sort of
a perspective, the academic question.
这就是定义和我所关注的
Here's that definition, and
as far as I'm concerned,
这是这个采访问题的正确答案，
this is the right answer to that
interview question from here forward,
直到有人告诉我另一个答案
until somebody tells me a different
answer, a different definition that
比这还多我没有来过
is more distilled than this,
which I haven't come across.
这就是问题的正确答案，什么是封闭的 ?
This is the right answer to that question,
what is closure?
关闭功能是当功能能够记住和
Closure is when a function
is able to remember and
进入它的词法范围本身之外的变量，
access its lexical scope,
the variables outside of itself,
所谓的自由变量，当它能进入这个词法范围时，
so-called free variables, when it's
able to access that lexical scope,
即使该函数在另一作用域中执行时也是如此。
even when that function
executes in a different scope.
让我们把第一部分
Let's take that first part.
该关闭可以访问其词法作用域。
That closure is able to
access its lexical scope.
我们已经知道了
We already know that.
这本身就是词法范围，是函数可以在外部引用变量
That is lexical scope in itself, is that
a function can reference variables outside
它本身就会在范围内找到它
of itself and it just goes up
the scope chain to find it.
第二部分是关键部分，没有这两部分，
The second part is the critical part,
and without these two parts,
你就没有了结了
you don't have closure.
你必须得两者都有
You have to have both.
没有第二部分，它只是词法范围。
Without the second part,
it's just lexical scope.
此定义的第二部分，即，即使是函数
With the second part of this definition,
which is, even when the function
在不同的范围内被执行，现在我们开始看到一些有趣的东西。
is executed in a different scope,
now we start to see something interesting.
当您执行函数并将其作为回调传递时，
Cuz when you take a function and
you pass it as a callback, or
你去做一个功能，把它退回去，它原来的范围
you take a function and return it back,
and the scope that it was originally
以其他方式定义，至少在概念上消失。
defined in has otherwise,
at least conceptually, gone away.
我们会认为，通常都是垃圾收集的，已经完成了。
And we would think, normally,
it's been garbage collected, it's done.
但有一种功能是在这个范围内定义的。
But there's a function that survived
that was defined within that scope.
原来这个范围根本就不存在。
It turns out that the scope
didn't go away at all.
事实证明，这一功能能够保持对该范围的引用，并且
It turns out that this function is able to
hold on to a reference to that scope, and
只要你通过这一功能，它就会继续得到这个功能。
wherever you pass the function,
it continues to have access to that.
这不是偶然的。
That doesn't happen by accident.
这不是魔法那是封闭的
That's not magical, that's closure.
保存，链接回到定义的原始作用域，
The preservation, the linkage back to
the original scope where it was defined,
无论你在哪里通过这个价值
no matter where you pass that value,
无论在何处执行，它都保留该值。
no matter where it executes,
it retains that value.
它保留了这个范围。
It preserves that scope.
这叫封闭
That's called closure.
让我们来看看几个例子，
So let's take a look at
a couple of examples,
你肯定会认出来的
ones that you'll probably
recognize right off the bat.
当然，你们都在某个时间点，或者在另一个时间，设置了一个设置的超时或
Surely, all of you have done a timer at
some point or another, a set timeout or
我敢打赌当你向你的计时器传递一个功能的时候
a set interval, and I bet when you
passed in a function to your timer,
它引用了自身以外的变量
it referenced some variable
outside of itself.
也可能是你从来没有考虑过，那是怎么做的呢 ?
What's also probably true is you never
stopped to consider, how does that work?
因为在此函数 waitASec 运行时，
Because at the time that
this function waitASec runs,
请求功能已完成，并且
the ask function has already finished, and
它的封闭问题应该已经结束了
the variable question which its
closed over should have gone away.
但它没有消失因为封闭了它
But it didn't go away
because closure preserved it,
所谓的 waitASec 函数在变量问题上关闭。
so-called the waitASec function is
closed over the variable question.
那是封闭的好吗
That's a closure, okay?
现在，在学术上，他们认为每个变量都是封闭的，
Now, academically, they think about
closure on a per variable basis,
只意味着我要关闭的变量
meaning only the variables
that I'm closed over,
这些是唯一保留的
those are the only ones
that are preserved.
从技术上来说，有可能是这样的情况。
Technically, it's possible
that that could be the case.
当然，这只会是你可以观察到的。
Certainly, that would only
be what you could observe.
但我要提醒你，一般来说，
But I would caution you to
consider that generally speaking,
至少我最新的信息是 JavaScript 引擎
at least the latest information that I
have, JavaScript engines essentially
将关闭实现为与整个作用域的链接，而不是基于每个变量。
implement closure as a linkage to the
entire scope, not on a per variable basis.
从技术上来说，它们应该能够关闭单个变量或
Technically, they should be able to
close over individual variables or
除去未结束的变量，但是
remove variables that aren't closed over,
but
基本上，据我所知，封闭的范围是在每个范围内。
essentially, as far as I'm aware,
closure is on a per scope basis.
所以如果你有一个可变的可变数据块
So if you have a variable that's holding
on to a really big piece of data and
你就会创造一个封闭的即使你没在引用它
then you create a closure,
even if you're not referencing it,
这些数据可能会被人所收集的垃圾
that data may stick around and
not get garbage collected.
所以最好的假设是封闭即使在学术上是每个变量
So it's best to assume that closure, even
though academically it's per variable,
最好是假设闭包是基于作用域的操作。
it's best to assume closure
is a scope-based operation.
这不是你要做的事
And it's not something you have
to do special with a function,
除了你还得在外面
other than you just have to
access a variable outside and
那你就得去别的地方了
then you have to pass
the function somewhere.
你要做的就是观察封闭存在的概念。
That's all you have to do to observe
the idea that closure exists.
想想如果你有一个没有关闭的功能会是什么样的情况。
Think about what it would be like if you
had a function that didn't have closure.
如果您使用的是具有第一类函数的语言，那么为词汇作用域，但是
If you're in a language that had first
class functions, lexical scope, but
没有关闭你就会在某个地方传递这个功能
didn't have closure,
you'd pass this function somewhere, and
突然，它会忘记它的所有变量。
all over sudden,
it would forget about all its variables.
没那么有用吗
Wouldn't be that helpful, would it?
几乎就像在必要时关闭是必要的
It's almost as if closure falls out as
a necessary requirement, a necessary
具有第一类函数的词性限定语言的第三个组件。
third component of a lexically scoped
language with first class functions.
如果你有那两个
If you have those two,
你会被封锁的因为这不可能
you're gonna have closure because
it wouldn't make sense not to.
这就是关闭的原因。
That's what closure is.
不管你是否做过计时器你肯定都写过
And whether you do timers or not,
you've certainly all written or
至少返回了函数或
at least accessed code
that returns functions or
把它们在回调中传递到同样的事情
passes them around in callbacks,
and that's the exact same thing.
如果我在此返回在问题变量上关闭的函数，
If I returned a function here that is
closed over the question variable,
那么即使这个要求的功能已经完成了，第 11 行，
then even though the ask function
has finished, by line 11,
我们仍能接触到那个变量
we still have access to that variable.
不是变量的快照，而是实际变量本身。
Not a snapshot of the variable,
but the actual variable itself.
这叫封闭
That's called closure.